http://www.springboardforthearts.org/privacy-policy/

Professional Services Directory
Minnesota Lawyers for the Arts (MnLA)
Contact & Locations
Move to University Avenue!
Professional Services Directory
Minnesota Lawyers for the Arts (MnLA)
Contact & Locations
Move to University Avenue!
Privacy Policy
SPRINGBOARD FOR THE ARTS PRIVACY POLICYThank you for visiting springboardforthearts.org. As an extension of our nonprofit mission, we want your visit to springboardforthearts.org and our sub-domain Sites to assist you. We know you don’t want the information you provide us shared indiscriminately. Here we explain what information Springboard for the Arts collects, what we do with the information, and what controls you have over the information collected. We’re committed to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information, and to protecting your ability to make financial transactions and transmit your personal data with full confidence.The privacy policy set forth here refers solely to springboardforthearts.org. Please read it carefully, and if you have any questions or concerns, please contact us. Also, note that springboardforthearts.org links to numerous other sites, particularly in our Resources section. Please consult those sites to learn more about their policies, as this privacy policy applies solely to springboardforthearts.org.1. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe collect two types of information from you: a) Personally identifiable information, which includes personal information (such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) that you voluntarily supply upon request when you register for a workshop or event, make a donation, apply for the Incubator program, purchase a job posting, request health vouchers, complete a survey, sign up for one of our newsletters or provide your e-mail address; and b) Non-personally identifiable information, for example IP Addresses and cookies, which includes tracking information collected as you navigate through our site. Uses of this information are discussed in Section 2 below.A. Personally Identifiable InformationWe will not collect personally identifiable information from you, other than what you supply to us on a voluntary basis upon request.Paid Products and Services: While the use of our site is free, we charge fees for some services, such as, but not limited to, workshop registration and job book listing purchases. To enable the purchase of these and other products or services, we ask you to provide personally identifiable information that is necessary to complete the transaction. Typically this information is requested via GiveMN.org or PayPal.com and may include your telephone number, e-mail address, billing address and credit card information. Springboard for the Arts does not collect or retain credit card information.Support of Springboard for the Arts: On certain pages within the Site we may now or in the future offer visitors the opportunity to make a donation in support of Springboard for the Arts and/or to our Incubator projects. If a visitor chooses to make a donation, he or she will be directed to GiveMN.org, which asks donors to provide certain personal information, such as but not limited to: first name, last name, email address, mailing address and credit card information. Please refer to GiveMN’s Privacy Policy (http://givemn.razoo.com/p/privacy_policy) for complete details.Springboard for the Arts does NOT request or receive credit card information from any third party, including GiveMN.org. However, GiveMN.org does provide a donor report/summary to Springboard for the Arts that includes the donor’s name, date of donation, address, email, designation and dedication (as applicable), payment method and amount of donation.Forums, Feedback and Content Submissions: On certain pages within the Site you can submit content to be published, make comments, suggestions, and complete surveys. We may collect your name, address, and e-mail addresses in connection with these activities. We will indicate which information is required and which is optional. We may contact users regarding their submissions in certain circumstances.Surveys, Special Offers, Mailings, and Events: On occasion, we may collect personal information from users in connection with optional surveys or special offers. We will indicate which information is required and which is optional. Such information will be used as indicated at the time of collection.Springboard for the Arts reserves the right to use contact information gathered on this website to communicate with individuals about Springboard events, offerings and programs. In compliance with Minnesota law, we do not sell, trade or share e-mail addresses with any unaffiliated third parties. As part of the Minnesota Audience Development Exchange, Springboard reserves the right to exchange mailing address lists with partner organizations for the purposes of developing stronger arts audiences in Minnesota.E-Mail and E-mail Newsletters: On occasion, we may collect personal information from users in connection with optional email and e-mail newsletters. We will indicate which information is required and which is optional. Such information will be used as indicated at the time of collection.B. Non-personally Identifiable InformationIn addition to information that you provide to us, we may also collect and store certain non-personally identifiable information automatically when you use the Site. This information helps us improve the experience you and other visitors have with the Site.For example, we may collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain, as well as related information such as the date on which you visit the Site. This information does not identify you personally and is only used in the aggregate.As is common practice among web sites, we use “cookies” and similar technologies. In general, cookies — the informational files that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website — are used on this Site to track and analyze how you and other visitors use our Site. We may now or in the future use these cookies in order to improve the Site, to identify the source of visitors and what pages you use while on our site, to offer visitors interactive and/or personalized features that would not be possible without the cookies, to recall specific information to save visitors time when they return to the Site, to provide our sponsors targeted sponsorship opportunities, to provide visitors customized sponsorship messages or list of customized videos of interest, and to identify usage and statistical trends. By looking at this traffic we can better understand our community, which allows us to improve our Site and to provide better service. At no time does the cookie reveal your name, address, or e-mail address (even if you have entered these in specific areas of the Site). The Site pages cannot extract any personally identifying information about you from what we receive via a cookie and your browser.You can set your browser preferences to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent.2. HOW WE USE INFORMATION GATHERED ON THE SITE Springboard for the Arts will not willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online users to any non-affiliated third party without first receiving the user’s permission, unless required by law.In terms of our own use of information, we may use your personally identifiable information for the activities described in the previous sections, for the activities described when you submitted the information, or for internal administrative purposes.We will typically explain the extent of use at the time you are asked to provide personal information. If you do not want this information to be collected or used by us for these purposes, you can simply “opt out.” Under certain circumstances, opting out may prevent your participation in activities for which personal information is needed, as in registering for workshops.In certain cases, we partner with other organizations to help provide services, for example we partner with the Hennepin County Library and other organizations to host workshops in various locations. These organizations may require you to register for a workshop on their Site, in which case it will be very clear that you are registering via a partner website, and not via springboardforthearts.org.Similarly, personally identifiable information provided in connection with a donation will be shared with third parties (such as GiveMN.org) who perform services to process the donation. In addition, Springboard for the Arts uses PayPal to complete some purchases, such as, but not limited to, the application fee for the Incubator program. Springboard for the Arts does NOT request or receive credit card information from any third party, including PayPal. However, PayPal provides payment and some personally identifiable information to Springboard for the Arts that includes the purchaser’s name, date of payment, address, email, designation and payment amount. Please refer to PayPal’s privacy policy for complete details.Springboard for the Arts will not sell, rent, lease, loan, trade, give, donate, transfer or exchange their membership or donor names to, with or from any local, state, or federal candidate for public office, authorized committee for such a candidate, or political party for any purpose whatsoever, except as required by law.We will not sell, exchange, or lend e-mail addresses to any non-affiliated third party, without your permission. However, we or our service providers may release personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency, or such release is necessary to protect anyone’s rights, property or safety.If at any time you would like to check or update our record of your information, please let us know by using the springboardforthearts.org Contact Us page, calling Springboard for the Arts  (651-292-4381, Monday-Friday, 9am-5pm CST), or writing to us (Springboard for the Arts, 308 Prince Street, Suite 270, Saint Paul, MN 55101).On certain pages, we may now or in the future, offer visitors the opportunity to provide comments, messages or other user-generated text, content or materials (collectively “User Materials”). Any information that you disclose when posting a message to these areas, such as your name, becomes public. In addition, the information that you disclose in these areas may be used by us for promotional and marketing purposes. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to disclose in these public areas. Further, Springboard for the Arts may use, copy, sublicense, modify, transmit, publicly perform, display, create derivative works of, host, index, cache, tag, encode, and/or adapt any User Materials, and any information contained therein, in any and all media formats or channels, whether now known or hereafter devised, including, but not limited to, the Site, other third party web sites, over the air (on radio or television), and on mobile platforms.We reserve the right to send you e-mail relating to administration, such as order confirmations, renewal/expiration notices, notices of credit-card problems, other transactional e-mails and notifications about major changes to our Site and/or to our Privacy Policy. If you have registered for online discussions or other services, you may receive e-mail specific to your participation in those activities.We offer several e-mail newsletters and emails. We will always provide a clear and convenient method of unsubscribing to our e-mailings. If you no longer wish to receive a specific newsletter, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions located in each newsletter or email, or by going to the Site’s Contact Us page and send us a message. We will update our records as soon as possible.Springboard for the Arts uses non-identifying aggregate information to analyze use of and better design the Site and to share with third parties in aggregate form only as appropriate. For example, we may tell a third party that a certain number of users accessed the job book on our Site. However, we will not disclose any information that could be used to identify those users.3. SECURITY OF INFORMATION Springboard for the Arts has in place what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. You should, however, keep in mind that no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. Because most e-mail is not encrypted, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.4. CHILDREN’S GUIDELINES Springboardforthearts.org is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect or store personally identifiable information about children under the age of 13.5. CORRECTIONS TO PERSONAL DATA; OPTING OUT Please Contact Us to a) correct or update any personal information in the Springboard for the Arts database that you state is erroneous, b) opt-out of future communications from Springboard for the Arts, or c) request Springboard for the Arts to make reasonable efforts to remove your personal information from the Springboard for the Arts online database, thereby canceling your newsletter registration and any other Springboard for the Arts registrations. This will not necessarily remove previous public comments and other User Materials submitted for public display on the Site. You should understand that it may be impossible to delete personal information entirely because of backups and records of deletions.6. ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR springboardforthearts.org By using this Site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy for springboardforthearts.org. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this Site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of springboardforthearts.org following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.7. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY Whenever this Privacy Policy for our Site changes, we will post the changes to the Site, and such changes will be effective immediately upon posting. If you do not agree to the changes, please do not continue to use the Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Site or sending you an e-mail if we have your e-mail address.If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, send us an email at info@springboardforthearts.org.
Saint Paul
contact | directions
262 University Ave West
Saint Paul, MN 55103
open M-F, 9:30-5PM
Visit the Resource Center
Fergus Falls
contact | directions
201 West Lincoln Ave.
